It's time to step back into the spotlight
Kiss of the Spider Woman is a romance, music,
drama film directed by Bill Condon.
Valentín, a political prisoner, shares a cell with Molina, a
window dresser convicted of public indecency.
The two form an unlikely bond as Molina recounts the plot of a Hollywood
musical starring his favorite silver screen diva, Ingrid Luna.
Valentín Arregui / Armando, played by Diego Luna.
Luis Molina / Kendall Nesbitt, played by Tonatiuh.
Ingrid Luna / Aurora / The Spider Woman, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Warden Ledesma, played by Bruno Bichir.
Marta, played by Josefina Scaglione.
Paolina Paz, played by Aline Mayagoitia.
Kiss of the Spider Woman is a 2025 American musical drama film written and directed by Bill Condon, based on the 1992
stage musical, itself based on Manuel Puig's 1976 novel (which had been previously adapted in 1985).
It stars Diego Luna, Tonatiuh, and Jennifer Lopez.
The film had its world premiere at the 2025 Sundance Film Festival on January
26, where it received generally positive reviews from critics.
It was released theatrically in the United States on October 10, by
Lionsgate Films, Roadside Attractions and LD Entertainment.
It was a box-office bomb, grossing $2 million against
a production budget of $30 million.
The film explores themes of prison, based on novel or
book, politics, homophobia, male friendship.
The tone is emotional and intense.